{
    "Questions":
    [
        {
        "Question":"Who was Ethosh's 1st paid customer?",
        "Option1":"Omkar Engineering",
        "Option2":"Ameya Transmission",
        "Option3":"Crompton Greaves",
        "Option4":"Persistent",
        "Correct":"Omkar Engineering"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who was the 1st US customer of Ethosh?",
        "Option1":"Agilent",
        "Option2":"Eaton",
        "Option3":"Biosensing",
        "Option4":"Bayer",
        "Correct":"Eaton"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who was the 1st VR customer of Ethosh?",
        "Option1":"Bayer",
        "Option2":"Agilent",
        "Option3":"Nanostring",
        "Option4":"Indian Navy",
        "Correct":"Indian Navy"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What industry Agilent is in?",
        "Option1":"Labtech",
        "Option2":"Medtech",
        "Option3":"Life sciences",
        "Option4":"Agriculture",
        "Correct":"Labtech"
        },
        {
        "Question":"For which client have we done maximum 3D videos?",
        "Option1":"Crompton Greaves",
        "Option2":"Bayer",
        "Option3":"Agilent",
        "Option4":"Kirloskar",
        "Correct":"Crompton Greaves"
        },
        {
        "Question":"For which project did Ethosh win CII award?",
        "Option1":"CG Maintenance Guides",
        "Option2":"Navy VR",
        "Option3":"Agilent AR",
        "Option4":"Kirloskar Roadrailer",
        "Correct":"Navy VR"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Which was Ethosh's 1st AR app that got launched on Appstore?",
        "Option1":"Agilent AR",
        "Option2":"Bayer Flex App",
        "Option3":"Zivira AR App",
        "Option4":"Pepsi AR",
        "Correct":"Zivira AR App"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Where does Ethosh not have a client?",
        "Option1":"US",
        "Option2":"India",
        "Option3":"Singapore",
        "Option4":"Australia",
        "Correct":"Singapore"
        },
        {
        "Question":"For which of the following services Agilent is yet to hire Ethosh?",
        "Option1":"3D videos",
        "Option2":"VR",
        "Option3":"AR",
        "Option4":"Veeva",
        "Correct":"Veeva"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Why our clients love us?",
        "Option1":"Good looking people",
        "Option2":"Sweet talkers",
        "Option3":"Young crowd",
        "Option4":"Quality",
        "Correct":"Quality"
        }
    ]
}
